spadepot.com 2016-11-28

# Privacy Policy | SpaDepot.com

Last Updated: January 2016

By using the SpaDepot.com (website of The Spa Depot, Inc.), engaging with us on social media, interacting with us in any way, or utilizing any of our services, you consent to this Privacy Policy.

If we collect information from you, we use it only for the purposes for which it was collected, and the other limited purposes outlined below. We do no sell your personally identifiable information including your email address to any third party and do not share this information with anyone not affiliated with The Spa Depot, Inc. except in the event of a transfer our business assets or as outlined below.

SpaDepot.com uses many sophisticated measures to ensure that customer information is safe and protected from misuse. The following discloses our online information gathering and dissemination practices. 

Please review our  **[Terms of Use](http://www.spadepot.com/terms-of-use.htm)**  which also governs your use of SpaDepot.com

WEBSITE ACTIVITY AND USAGE

The Spa Depot Inc. collects some non-personally identifiable information automatically with your use of the SpaDepot.com website. This may include, but is not limited to, your IP address, the type of browser or operating system you use, the domain name from which you linked to our site, general demographic information, and clicks and activity on SpaDepot.com. This anonymous usage information generally is not associated with your personal information. We use this non-personally identifiable information to help make our website more user-friendly. We may share this information with our third-party business partners on an aggregated basis.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

When you create an account on or purchase from SpaDepot.com, engage with us on social media, answer our surveys, or interact with us in any way, you may choose to give us personal information, such as: your name, email address, phone number or credit card numbers.

This personal information allows us to process your transactions, provide quality customer service, and order tracking or delivery service information. The decision to provide this information is entirely optional, however if you choose not to provide the requested information, you may not be able to access all or some of the features on SpaDepot.com.

We will never sell your personally identifiable data to any third party that is not an affiliate of The Spa Depot, Inc. unless: (i) we transfer of our business assets; (ii) we first obtain permission from you; (iii) we need to share it with agents or contractors who perform services for us regarding the processing of your online order(s) or other business you conduct with us; or (iv) we are required by law to disclose it.

SpaDepot.com uses “cookies” to track information about your activity on our website. These cookies are used to provide better online marketing based on your interests and preferences. Our cookies will never track or save highly confidential information from your hard drive such as your email address, passwords, or credit card numbers.

You, the user, have the option to modify most browsers to accept cookies, send notification when a cookie is sent, or reject all cookies. If you choose to reject cookies, you may no longer be able to utilize certain services or features on SpaDepot.com

The Spa Depot, Inc. utilizes various social media channels such as Facebook, Twitter, Blogs, Instagram and Pinterest as channels for customer service, marketing promotions, and information. If you contact us on one of these platforms, we may contact you via direct message. By contacting us through these platforms you consent to this privacy policy, as well as the policy of the relevant social media platform.

If you have chosen to share your personal information, The Spa Depot, Inc. may use this information to communicate with you in order to: provide superior customer service, offer promotions, update you on your order status, or ask questions about your order.

By signing up for a SpaDepot.com account, you agree to receive emails, newsletters and other communications from SpaDepot.com and their affiliates. If you would like to opt out of receiving these types of communications you many instruct SpaDepot.com to stop sending you email, newsletters or other information by following the ‘unsubscribe’ instructions provided in the email.

The Spa Depot, Inc. may work with third party companies in order to provide you with personalized email’s, marketing or promotional offers. Cookies are used in these email messages for analytical purposes and to help us measure their effectiveness.

The Spa Depot, Inc. may also use email to contact customers regarding issues with their transactions and for order tracking.

The Spa Depot Inc. will never knowingly solicit to or accept personally identifiable information from users known to be under thirteen (13) years of age. By accepting these Terms you certify that you are either (i) 18 years of age or older (ii) 13 years of age or older under the supervision of a legal guardian who has agreed to these terms on your behalf.

If it is determined that a child under the age of 13 has provided personal information on our website, this information will be deleted.

The Spa Depot, Inc. may at times contract with other companies to serve you better. These companies assistance can help us manage and store customer data, track purchases, send marketing, run promotions and provide other services.

SpaDepot.com may contain links to other websites. The Spa Depot, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

The Spa Depot, Inc. takes all reasonable steps to ensure the safety of your personally identifiable information. SpaDepot.com has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of your personal information under our control. SpaDepot.com utilizes Extended Validation Secure Sockets Layer (EV SSL) and some of the highest technology available today for secure commerce transactions. The Spa Depot, Inc. does not assume any liablility for third-party usage of your personal information, whether obtained legally or illegally from our system.

The Spa Depot, Inc. reserves the right, at any time in our sole discretion, to update or modify this Privacy Policy and/or the website at any time without notice. Your use of the SpaDepot.com website following any such change constitutes your consent to the revised Privacy Policy. The revised Privacy Policy shall replace and void all previous versions.

CONTACT US:

The Spa Depot  
8910 Select Ct SE  
Olympia, WA 98501-5740 U.S.A

(800) 823 3638
